Facilities Planning Building File 1945-1980
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Facilities Planning Building File
1945-1980
1965-1970
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Archives 106
6 containers 7 linear feet
Records consist of correspondence, reports, bidding records, and other documents related to architecture work and construction.
History:
An University Architect has served as the construction officer of Washington State University from 1911 onward. The modern form of the office dates from 1947, when it became a full-time, staffed administrative department. In 1967, the office was renamed as Facilities Planning and later as Facilities Development. It is responsible for the major construction projects of the university.
The records consist of correspondence, reports, bidding records, and other documents related to architecture work and construction.
Records of the University Architect/Facilities Planning are arranged according the building number system that identifies structures owned by Washington State University. The archival arrangement of the records follows the office practice without variance.
Locating records revenant to a specific project or building requires having the building number available.
The Collection is open for research use.
This portion of the University Architect/Facilities Planning building file was transferred to university archives in 1981 (UA81-11) and 1982 (UA82-09), in accordance with approved records schedules.
Washington State University. Department of Facilities Planning--Archives; Washington State University. University Architect.; State College of Washington. University Architect.; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Planning--Records and correspondence; Washington State University--Buildings--History--Archives
College buildings--Washington (State)--Designs and plans
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities; Architecture
- Old Administration Building Remodeling (Foreign Language Building) - Bldg. 1
  - Budget (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - DHEW Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Program (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DeNeff, Debble & Barton, Correspondence, 6/67-4/69 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DeNeff, Debble & Barton, Correspondence, 5/69-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - DeNeff, Debble & Barton, Contracts & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - S.G. Morin & Son, Inc., Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - S.G. Morin & Son, Inc., Contracts, Payments, C.O.s (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Fulmer Hall Annex - Bldg. 3
  - Building Vibration Report (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Marque, Clerc & Riley, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bohler Gym, Remodeling of Coaches Offices - Bldg. 11
  - Budget (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corres., 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corresp., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Selkirk Company, Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Selkirk Company, Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commercial Builders, Inc., Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Commercial Builders, Inc., Contract, Payments & C.O.s (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mott Electric Co., Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mott Electric Co., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Smith Gym Remodeling - Bldg. 12
  - Renaming, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Selkirk Co., Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Selkirk Co., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mott Electric Co., Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Mott Electric Co., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 37)
- McCroskey Hall - Bldg., 19
  - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Carpenter Hall - Bldg. 20
  - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Maintenance Building - Bldg. 21
  - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- President's Residence Remodel - Bldg. 31
  - Budget (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Prospectus (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Trogdon & Smith, Archs., Corres., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Trogdon & Smith, Archs., Construction Reports (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Trogdon & Smith, Archs., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Sceva Construction Co., Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Budget, Sprinkler System & Landscaping (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Sceva Construction Co., Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - L. Keith Hellstrom, Lands. Arch., Corres., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Nelson Landscape Service, Corres., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Nelson Landscape Service, Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Rejected Bids, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Rejected Bids, Landscaping (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Troy Hall Elevator - Bldg. 36
  - General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Budget (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Contract, Payments & C.O.s (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - C&S Builders, Inc., Contract, Payments & C.O.s (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - C&S Builders, Inc., General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Van Doren Hall - Bldg. 37
  - General Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Wilson Hall Alterations - Bldg. 40
  - Budget (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - General Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - General Conditions for Rural Sociology & Sociology (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Musgrove & Marshall, Archs., General Corres., 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Musgrove & Marshall, Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Vern W. Johnson & Sons, Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Vern W. Johnson & Sons, Contract & Change Orders (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Wegner Hall - Bldg. 45
  - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Engineering Lab Building - Bldg. 46
  - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Endoparasite Vector Laboratory - Bldg. 47
  - General Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Sewage - Bldg. 51
  - Correspondence, Contract & Payments, 1946-1951 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Todd Hall - Bldg. 55
  - General Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Shock Dynamics Laboratory - Bldg. 56
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - L.C. Campbell, Contract & Change Orders (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Mining Experiment Station - Bldg. 57
  - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- W.J. Spillman Hall - Bldg. 59
  - General Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Ernest Holland Library - Bldg. 62
  - General Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Barnard & Holloway, Archs., Corres., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Student Bookstore - Bldg. 64
  - Dedicatory Plaque, General Corres., 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Kreugel, McAllister, Neill Halls - Bldg. 69
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Nuclear Radiation Center - Bldg. 74
  - General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Johnson Hall - Bldg. 76
  - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Gannon-Goldsworthy Hall - Bldg. 79
  - Shower Floors, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Streit-Perham Hall - Bldg. 81
  - Architect's Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Safety Building Renovation - Bldg. 84
  - Program (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Corres., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Comparative Behavior Lab. Addition - Bldg. 90
  - Budget (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - NIH Application & Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - General Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Victor L. Wulff, Arch., Corres., 1965-4/1966 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Victor L. Wulff, Arch., Corres., 5/66-1969 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Victor L. Wulff, Arch., Corres., 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Victor L. Wulff, Arch., Contract & Change Orders (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Victor L. Wulff, Arch., Inspection Reports (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Diary Inspection Reports (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Commercial Builders, Inc., Corres., 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Commercial Builders, Inc., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Finish Hardware & Keying Schedule (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - University of Idaho, Testing, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Lab., Concrete Testing, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Weston Mechanical Contractors, Corres., 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Weston Mechanical Contractors, Contracts, Payments, C.O.s (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Ray Dillon Electric Co., Inc., Corres., 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Ray Dillon Electric Co., Inc., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Rejected Bids, General (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Publications Court - Bldg. 91
  - Washington Testing Labs., Soils Investigation (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Budget (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Program (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - General Correspondence 1969-1971 & Diary Inspec. Reports (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Contract, Payments & C.O.s (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Commercial Builders, Corres., 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Commercial Builders, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 2, Folder 129)
- C. Clement French Administration Bldg. - Bldg. 92
  - Budget (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Program (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - General Correspondence, 1962-6/1965 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - General Correspondence, 7/65-1966 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Shannon & Wilson, Inc., Soils Eng., Pile Driving (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Shannon & Wilson, Inc., Soils Eng., Rept. on Found. Invest. (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Kirk, Wallace, McKinley, Archs., Corres., 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Kirk, Wallace, McKinley, Archs., Corres., 1/66 - 5/66 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Kirk, Wallace, McKinley, Archs., Corres., 6/66 - 10/70 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Kirk, Wallace, McKinley, Archs., Job Conference Notes (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Kirk, Wallace, McKinley, Archs., Contract & C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - James B. Notkin, Mech. Eng., Corres., 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Thomas E. Sparling., Elec. Eng., Corres., 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - HEFA Correspondence, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Christiansen Brothers, Inc., Corres., 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Christiansen Brothers, Inc., Contract & C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Finish Hardware (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - General Corres., Testing, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Labs., Concrete Testing (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Washington Testing Labs., Concrete Testing (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Mech. Eng., Corres., 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Mech. Eng., Contract & C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Kehne-Crabtree Electric Co., Contract & C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Kehne-Crabtree Electric Co., Corres., 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Bank & Office Interiors, Inc., Corres & P.O.s (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Richard Haag Assoc., Lands. Arch., Corres., 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Stanek's Nurseries, Inc., Corres., 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Stanek's Nurseries, Inc., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Rejected Bids, General Construction (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Rejected Bids, Landscape (Box 3, Folder 163)
- President's Office Completion - Bldg. 92
  - Budget (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Walter, Dorwin, Teague, Archs., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Walter, Dorwin, Teague, Archs., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Stephenson Residence Center, Bldg. "D" - Bldg. 93
  - Budget (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - HHFA Project Summary (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - General Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - General Correspondence, Architects (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Walker, McGough, Foltz, Archs., Corres., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Walker, McGough, Foltz, Archs., Corres., 1/68 - 7/69 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Walker, McGough, Foltz, Archs., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Construction Conference Notes (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Diary-Inspection Reports (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Electrical Consultants, Corres., 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Alfred Brown Co., Extra Work Reports (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Alfred Brown Co., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Alfred Brown Co., Corres., 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Finish Hardware (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Testing (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Shannon & Wilson, Inc., Soils Eng., Found. Investigation (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - United States Testing Co., Concrete Testing (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Snelson, Inc., Mech. Contractor, Contract & C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Snelson, Inc., Mech. Contractor, Corres., 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Kehne-Crabtree Electric Co., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Kehne-Crabtree Electric Co., Contract & C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Furnishings, Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Spokane Dry Goods, Inc., Contract, Payments & C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Serta Mattress Co., Contract, Payments & C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Walker & McGough, Daily Inspec. Reports, 3/68-12/68 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Magna Design, Inc., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Nelson Landscape Service, Corres., 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Nelson Landscape Service, Contract & Change Orders (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Rejected Bids, General (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - Rejected Bids, Landscaping (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Rejected Bids, Furnishings (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - Rejected Bids, Furnishings, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 202)
- Parking Area South of Forest - Bldg. 93
  - HHFA, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - General Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - Kenneth W. Brooks, Arch., Contract & C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - Kenneth W. Brooks, Arch., Corres., 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 206)
  - Max J. Kuney Co., Corres., 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Max J. Kuney Co., Contract & Change Orders (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - V. Eugene Cameron, Surveying (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 4, Folder 210)
- Johnson Tower - Bldg. 94
  - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 211)
- Wood Technology - Bldg. 95
  - Budget (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - Carlson & James, Archs., Corres., 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - Carlson & James, Archs., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - Commercial Builders, Inc., Corres., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 216)
  - Commercial Builders, Inc., Contract, Estimates, C.O.s (Box 4, Folder 217)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 4, Folder 218)
- Physical Education Building - Bldg. 96
  - Budget (Box 4, Folder 219)
  - HEFA Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 220)
  - Shannon & Wilson, Foundation Invest. Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 221)
  - Shannon & Wilson, Foundation Investigation (Box 4, Folder 222)
  - Program Statement (Box 4, Folder 223)
  - General Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 224)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-4/1969 (Box 4, Folder 225)
  - General Correspondence, 5/69 - 6/70 (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - General Correspondence, 7/70 -, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corres., 7/66 - 12/67 (Box 5, Folder 228)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corres., 1/68 - 4/69 (Box 5, Folder 229)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corres., 5/69 - 6/70 (Box 5, Folder 230)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Corres., 7/70 -, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 231)
  - Weekly Employment Record (Box 5, Folder 232)
  - Paddock & Hollingbery, Archs., Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 233)
  - Esvelt & Saxton, Consulting Engineers (Box 5, Folder 234)
  - Valentine, Fisher, Tomlinson, Consulting Engineers (Box 5, Folder 235)
  - Selkirk Co., Corres., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - Selkirk Co., Contract & Change Orders (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Keying Schedule (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Lab., Concrete Testing (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Corres., 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - Mott Electric Co., Inc., Corres., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - Mott Electric Co., Inc., Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - Rejected Bids, General (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 5, Folder 245)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 5, Folder 246)
- New Fine Arts Building - Bldg. 97
  - Phase 2 Space Requirements (Box 5, Folder 247)
- Insect Flight Room - Bldg. 111A
  - Budget (Box 5, Folder 248)
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 249)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - Douglas C. Durkoop, Arch., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 251)
  - Valley Builders, Corres., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 252)
  - Valley Builders, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 253)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 5, Folder 254)
- Controlled Environment Facilities - Bldg. 114
  - Budget (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - General Correspondence, 1966 - 6/68 (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - General Correspondence, 7/68 -, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 257)
  - ADSCO Construction Co., Corres., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 258)
  - ADSCO Construction Co., Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 259)
  - Concrete Testing (Box 5, Folder 260)
  - D. Bingham Mechanical Co., Corres., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 261)
  - D. Bingham Mechanical Co., Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 262)
  - Spence Electric Co., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 263)
  - Spence Electric Co., Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 264)
  - Rejected Bids, General (Box 5, Folder 265)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 5, Folder 266)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 5, Folder 267)
  - Rejected Bids, Electrical (Box 5, Folder 268)
  - Rejected Bids, Mechanical (Box 5, Folder 269)
- USDA Greenhouse - Bldg. 114H
  - General Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 270)
  - General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 271)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 272)
  - C&S Builders, Contract, C.O.s, Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 273)
  - General Machinery Co., Contract, C.O.s, Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 274)
  - B&W Utility Co., Contract, C.O.s, Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 275)
- Seed House - Bldg. 115
  - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 276)
- Hilltop Stables - Bldg. 151
  - General Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 5, Folder 277)
- Bee Research Labs - Bldg., 194
  - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 278)
  - Walter N. Varnum, Corres., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 279)
  - General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 280)
  - Walter N. Varnum, Contract & C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 281)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 5, Folder 282)
- Fur Farm and Apiary Relocation - Bldg., 197
  - Budget (Box 5, Folder 283)
  - General Correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 5, Folder 284)
  - Boyington & Reed, Archs., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 285)
  - Boyington & Reed, Archs., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 286)
  - J.J. Dodgen, Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 287)
  - J.J. Dodgen, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 5, Folder 288)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 5, Folder 289)
- Horse Disease Lab - Bldg. 197L
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - Neal Builders, Inc., Corres., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - Neal Builders, Inc., Contract & C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 294)
- Troposcatter Transmitter Facility - Bldg. 312
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 296)
  - C&S Builders, Corres., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - C&S Builders, Contract & Change Orders (Box 6, Folder 298)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 299)
- Intramural Fields - Bldg. 314
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - Robt. L. Woerner, Lands. Arch., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - Robt. L. Woerner, Lands. Arch., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Corres., 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - Warren, Little & Lund, Inc., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 305)
- Golf Course - Bldg. 365
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Robt. Muir Graves, ASGCA, Corres., 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - Robt. Muir Graves, ASGCA, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - Progress Report (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - Nelson Landscape Service, Corres., 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - Nelson Landscape Service, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 312)
- Golf Course & Intramural Service Bldgs. - Bldg. 365A
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - Adkison Architects, Corres., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Adkison Architects, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - Sceva Construction, Corres., 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - Sceva Construction, Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Golf Course Screens, Corres., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 321)
- Sheaf Storage Building - Bldg. 401F
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - Sceva Steel Buildings, Corres., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Sceva Steel Buildings, Contract & Change Orders (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 326)
- Rogers-Orton Dormitory - Bldg. 802
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 327)
  - Building Program (Box 6, Folder 328)
  - Lea, Pearson & Richards, Archs., Corres., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 329)
- Humanities Building - Bldg. 803
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 330)
  - Richard Haag Assoc., Lands. Arch., Corres., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - Facilities Planning, Phase I (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - Facilities Planning, Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 334)